Well, the next three riders in the order,
嗯，接下来三位按顺序的车手，
you know, of Vingar and the two Red Bulls,
你知道，是Vingar和两位红牛车队的车手，
were on time trial bikes.
他们骑的都是计时赛用车。
The Bremko Avanapal, who was the notable absentee, really,
Bremko Avanapal，这位备受关注的缺席者，说真的，
ended up 12th, having been second fastest through the first split,
最终获得第12名，在首个分段计时中曾是第二快的，
which would have been where the time trial bike
这正是计时赛用车最能发挥优势的地方，
would have had the maximum advantage and it all went backwards for him from then on.
本应能发挥最大优势的地方，但从那之后他的表现就一路下滑了。
But the second, third and fourth road time trial bikes, the winner, the dominant winner,
不过位列第二、第三和第四的公路计时赛用车的车手，以及那位获胜者，那位统治级别的获胜者，
I sort of think Pogacar could have done virtually any, you know,
我觉得波加查几乎骑任何车型都行，你知道，
could have gone up there on a Brompton and he probably would have won the time trial.
就算骑一辆Brompton折叠车去，他可能也会赢得这场计时赛。
We saw Renko the other day there at the back and I got in contact with the team and said,
前几天我们看到Renko在后面，我联系了团队并说，
why is he at the back? Why is he off the back?
为什么他在后面？为什么他落后了？
And he's just going back to the team car. There's something not right with Renko.
而他现在正要回到团队车辆那里。Renko有点不对劲。
He's not quite firing.
他现在状态不太对。
And he was almost humiliated in the time 12 yesterday.
而且他昨天（12号）的计时赛中差点就出糗了。
So let's see how he gets on today.
所以看看他今天表现怎么样吧。
I cannot think that for one moment he will be good today.
我一点也不觉得他今天会有好表现。
Well, crunching the numbers and Kieran Kelly is with the statistics.
嗯，在分析数据，Kieran Kelly正在处理统计数据。
Gives him some fantastic, really left field, some oddballed statistics.
给他看了一些很棒但非常非常规、很奇怪的统计数据。
But one that he's working on at the moment.
但有一个他现在正在研究的（数据）。
And we haven't got an absolute definitive clear certain answer.
我们还没有一个绝对明确、确定的答案。
But we believe that that's the first time that a reigning world time trial champion
但我们认为，这是现任世界计时赛冠军
has ever been caught in a time trial.
首次在计时赛中被追上。
And this Vingo catching him for two minutes yesterday.
而且昨天Vingo把他甩开了两分钟。
It's 95% sure on that one.
那一点95%确定。
Yeah, we might have had something maybe in the past.
是的，我们也许过去有过类似的情况。
I can't remember.
我记不清了。
Maybe in a prologue I can remember some stuff that was...
也许在序幕赛中，我记得一些事情是...
Important work working that one out.
弄清楚那件事是很重要的工作。
Cruising off the front of the moment.
在前方轻松骑行。
The Little Shracks have certainly been much in evidence in the early attacks.
The Little Shracks 无疑在早期的进攻中十分引人注目。
Quinn Simmons, Atis Gilmose and others.
Quinn Simmons、Atis Gilmose 和其他人。
It's a good one that they have.
他们拥有的这个很不错。
Trek notable really by having a bespoke water bottle.
Trek 确实因拥有一个定制水壶而引人注目。
Gives them a little bit of an aerodynamic advantage.
这给他们带来了一点空气动力学优势。